<Language Name="English" IsDefault="false" IsRightToLeft="false">
    <LocaleResource Name="Plugins.FriendlyName.SmartStore.Google.Analytics" AppendRootKey="false">
        <Value>Google Analytics</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="Plugins.Description.SmartStore.Google.Analytics" AppendRootKey="false">
        <Value>Adds Google Analytics tracking scripts to the shop.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="AdminInstruction">
        <Value>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Google Analytics is a free website statistics tool from Google. It keeps track of statistics about the visitors and ecommerce conversion on your website.</p>
                <p>Follow the next steps to enable Google Analytics integration:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><a href="http://www.google.com/analytics/" target="_blank">Create a Google Analytics account</a> and follow the wizard to add your website.</li>
                    <li>Copy the Google Analytics ID into the ID field below.</li>
                    <li>Activate the Google Analytics widget under <b>CMS > Widgets</b> to integrate Google Analytics into your store.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    Google Analytics  can analyze data from your customers even without the use of cookies.  
                    An anonymous client ID is used for this purpose. Only when a customer agrees to the use of analytical cookies in the cookie manager, 
                    cookies are also used by the Analytics script. 
                    If you also want the tag manager to become active only after the customer has agreed to the analytical cookies, 
                    please activate the <i>Load only with consent</i> option below.
                </p>
		        <p>
			        To include the opt-out cookie in your privacy policy, use the following code:
		        </p>
		        <pre>&lt;a href=&quot;javascript:gaOptout()&quot;&gt;Deactivate Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt;</pre>
              ]]>
        </Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="ScriptUpdateInfo">
        <Value>
            <![CDATA[
                This plugin uses an outdated script. Please click the <b>Restore Scripts</b> button further down this page to use the latest version.
            ]]>
        </Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="GoogleId">
        <Value>ID</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="GoogleId.Hint">
        <Value>Enter Google Analytics ID.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="RenderWithUserConsentOnly">
        <Value>Load only with consent</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="RenderWithUserConsentOnly.Hint">
        <Value>Specifies whether the Analytics script is loaded only after the customer consents to analytic cookies.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="TrackingScript">
        <Value>Tracking code with {ECOMMERCE} line</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="TrackingScript.Hint">
        <Value>Paste the tracking code generated by Google Analytics here. {GOOGLEID} and {ECOMMERCE} will be dynamically replaced.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="EcommerceScript">
        <Value>Tracking code for {ECOMMERCE} part, with {DETAILS} line</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="EcommerceScript.Hint">
        <Value>Paste the tracking code generated by Google analytics here. {ORDERID}, {TOTAL}, {TAX}, {SHIP}, {CITY}, {STATEPROVINCE}, {COUNTRY}, {DETAILS} will be dynamically replaced.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="EcommerceDetailScript">
        <Value>Tracking code for {DETAILS} part</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="EcommerceDetailScript.Hint">
        <Value>Paste the tracking code generated by Google analytics here. {ORDERID}, {PRODUCTSKU}, {PRODUCTNAME}, {CATEGORYNAME}, {UNITPRICE}, {QUANTITY} will be dynamically replaced.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="OptOutNotification">
        <Value>Tracking is now disabled</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="CookieInfo">
        <Value>Google Analytics helps us analyze and improve the user behavior of our website to provide you with the best possible user experience.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="ConsentAdUserData">
        <Value>By consenting to the transmission of advertising-related user data, you authorise us to transmit a unique identifier linked to your customer account to Google.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="ConsentAdPersonalization">
        <Value>If you allow personalised advertising, you will receive ads from Google services that are tailored to your personal interests.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="RestoreScripts">
        <Value>Restore scripts</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="RestoreScripts.Hint">
        <Value>Restores the original scripts. After a store update this function should be used to make sure that the latest scripts are used.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="RenderCatalogScripts">
        <Value>Track catalog</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="RenderCatalogScripts.Hint">
        <Value>Defines whether tracking scripts are rendered for lists in the product catalog.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="RenderCheckoutScripts">
        <Value>Track checkout</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="RenderCheckoutScripts.Hint">
        <Value>Specifies whether tracking scripts are rendered for events in the checkout process.</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="MinifyScripts">
        <Value>Minify scripts</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
    <LocaleResource Name="MinifyScripts.Hint">
        <Value>Specifies whether the generated scripts are minimized (recommended).</Value>
    </LocaleResource>
</Language>